
let questions1 = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which is not a type of secondary memory?",
    answer: "Random Access Memory (RAM)",
    options: [
      "Solid State Drive",
      "Hard Disk",
      "Random Access Memory (RAM)",
      "USB Pen Drive"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "IPv6 protocol defines an IP address of",
    answer: "128 bit",
    options: [
      "32 bit",
      "64 bit",
      "128 bit",
      "256 bit"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "A social network can be represented as",
    answer: "Graph",
    options: [
      "Graph",
      "Tree",
      "Star",
      "Ring"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Who among the following is known as the father of computing?",
    answer: "Charles Babbage",
    options: [
      "Charles Babbage",
      "Tim Berners Lee",
      "Philip Don Estridge",
      "James Gosling"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following displays the start menu in the Windows operating system?",
    answer: "Ctrl + Esc",
    options: [
      "Ctrl + Z",
      "Alt + Spacebar",
      "Ctrl + Esc",
      "Alt + Enter"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Microsoft Excel is a",
    answer: "Electronic Spreadsheet",
    options: [
      "MS office package",
      "Electronic Spreadsheet",
      "Graphic package",
      "Financial planning package"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which memory is both static and non-volatile?",
    answer: "ROM",
    options: [
      "CACHE",
      "ROM",
      "BIOS",
      "RAM"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The set of instructions which tell a computer what to do is called",
    answer: "Program",
    options: [
      "Matter",
      "Instructor",
      "Compiler",
      "Program"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the following is not an in-built software application found in MS Windows?",
    answer: "CD Player",
    options: [
      "Paint",
      "CD Player",
      "Disk Defragmenter",
      "Volume Control"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following comprise commonly used Assembly language?",
    answer: "ARM",
    options: [
      "ARM",
      "COBOL",
      "BASIC",
      "Python"
    ]
  },

];